let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Who founded Java Programming?",
      answer: "b) James Gosling",
      options: [
        "a) Guido van Rossum",
        "b) James Gosling",
        "c) Dennis Ritchie",
        "d) Bjarne Stroustrup"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "What part is used to compile, debug and execute java programs?",
      answer: "c) JDK",
      options: [
        "a) JRE",
        "b) JIT",
        "c) JDK",
        "d) JVM"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "What difference does it make when java is out of memory?",
      answer: "b) OutOfMemoryError",
      options: [
        "a) MemoryError",
        "b) OutOfMemoryError",
        "c) MemoryOutOfBoundsException",
        "d) MemoryFullException"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of these selection statements in Java do you have?",
      answer: "d) if ()",
      options: [
        "a) a break",
        "b) continue",
        "c) for ()",
        "d) if ()"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of these keywords is used to define interfaces in Java?",
      answer: "c) interface",
      options: [
        "a) intf",
        "b) Intf",
        "c) interface",
        "d) Interface"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following is the superclass of all Java classes?",
      answer: "c) Object class",
      options: [
        "a) Array List",
        "b) Abstract Class",
        "c) Object class",
        "d) String"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which of the following is not a Java Profiler?",
      answer: "c) JVM",
      options: [
        "a) JProfiler",
        "b) Eclipse Profile",
        "c) JVM",
        "d) JConsole"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of these packages contains the stack overflow variant in Java?",
      answer: "c) java.lang",
      options: [
        "a) java.io",
        "b) java.system",
        "c) java.lang",
        "d) java.util"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of these statements are wrong about Thread?",
      answer: "b) run () method is used to start a thread process before start the () method in special cases",
      options: [
        "a) start () method is used to start a thread function",
        "b) run () method is used to start a thread process before start the () method in special cases",
        "c) The thread can be created using only the runnable interface",
        "d) The thread can be made of a class that extends to the Thread class"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of these keywords is used to block an exception?",
      answer: "d) try",
      options: [
        "a) check",
        "b) throw",
        "c) catch",
        "d) try"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "Which of the following is not an access modifier?",
      answer: "b) Void",
      options: [
        "a) Protected",
        "b) Void",
        "c) Public",
        "d) Confidential"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "What is the range for the type of char data in Java?",
      answer: "c) 0 to 65535",
      options: [
        "a) 0 to 256",
        "b) -128 to 127",
        "c) 0 to 65535",
        "d) 0 to 32767"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "Which section provides for the implementation of the private server side of the system?",
      answer: "d) ServerSocket",
      options: [
        "a) Server",
        "b) ServerReader",
        "c) Socket",
        "d) ServerSocket"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "Which of the following is true of servers?",
      answer: "b) The resources operate within the web server’s domain, private domain and use the functionality of the java category libraries",
      options: [
        "a) Resources can use the full functionality of Java class libraries",
        "b) The resources operate within the web server’s domain, private domain and use the functionality of the java category libraries",
        "c) Applications run within the web server address area",
        "d) The servlets are independent in one place because they are labeled with java"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "What is the expansion of the compiled java classes?",
      answer: "c) .class",
      options: [
        "a) .txt",
        "b) .js",
        "c) .class",
        "d) .java"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "Arrays in java are-",
      answer: "b. Objects",
      options: [
        "a. Object References",
        "b. Objects",
        "c. Primitive Data type",
        "d. None"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "Total constructor string class have?",
      answer: "13",
      options: [
        "3",
        "7",
        "13",
        "20"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "Where does the system stores parameters and local variables whenever a method is invoked?",
      answer: "b. Stack",
      options: [
        "a. Heap",
        "b. Stack",
        "c. Array",
        "d. Tree"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "When is the finalize() method called?",
      answer: "a. Before Garbage Collection",
      options: [
        "a. Before Garbage Collection",
        "b. Before an object goes out of scope",
        "c. Before a variable goes out of scope",
        "d. None"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "What is Runnable?",
      answer: "b. Interface",
      options: [
        "a. Abstract class",
        "b. Interface",
        "c. Class",
        "d. Method"
      ]
    }
  ];
  